<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome to the Lonely Hackers Club on Lonely Hackers Club</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome to the Lonely Hackers Club on Lonely Hackers Club</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>DEF CON n00b guide</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/defcon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/defcon/</guid>
      <description>DEF CON Guide DEF CON Belonging (Sometimes You Feel Like a Nut. Sometimes You Don’t.) Getting Involved and Making New Hacker Friends  Be Inclusive (“Pac Man” Theory)  Transportation  Airport Tips/Tricks International Hackers Hotels Hotel Room Hax Work Trip?  “Doing The Con”  Badges LineCon DEF CON Program Navigating the Con Swag/Vendor Area Tracks/Talks RoomCon DC101 Villages Workshops Contests and Events CFP SkyTalks Parties  Con Life  3-2-1 Rule Handles Goons (Those Cool People in Red, Often Confused with Deadpool) $$$$ aka MONEY Pack Light, Have Comfortable Shoes Daily Loadout Medical Supplies/Medicine Badge Life/Indie Badges Con Flu Bathrooms Shenanigans Collectible/Swag Challenge Coins  Staying Informed  Hacker Tracker App Twitter Slack Reddit Lonely Hackers Club  Security/Privacy  Photos/Videos Device Security/Privacy Burner Devices Room Security/Privacy Personal Security/Safety Bring a Battle Buddy Being Stupid?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>books</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/books/</guid>
      <description>So you wanna get your learn on huh? Below is intended to be a growing list of books to help you level up those hacker skills
The Knowledgebase Hacking the Art of exploitation
Practical Malware Analysis
Practical Binary Analysis
Serious Cryptography
PoC or GTFO
PoC or GTFO Volume 2
Social Engineering: The Art of Human Hacking
Open Source intelligence Techniques
Black Hat Python</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>